I am Venerable Banmah Victor.
I'm a retired anglican priest.
I served the anglican communion for 15 years before I retired.
The woman next to me is the wife of my youth.
You must cherish the wife of your youth.
I'm getting to 82 years.
Venerable Banmah Victor & Wife
Retired Anglican Priest
Emmanuel TV Testimony
The story I'm about to tell you is
what the motto of this church is - that distance is not a barrier.
I am of the anglican communion.
As you will know how people behave - I should not have anything to do with The SCOAN.
But the faith of God - if you demonstrate it, if you have it,
you can tell that mountain to move and it will move.
A mountain is not a physical thing. It's not. It does not exist anywhere.
Illness is a mountain and that is what I had.
I had pains in my ear.
And you know if you have pain in your ear, you will lose your balance.
So I started to fall in places where I thought I didn't need to.
Sometimes, I would fall in my room.
So I was afraid that I may not be able to attain the age of 81 that I am today.
But one night, my wife scrolled down to Emmanuel TV.
And I was there. I was sitting down lazily; I was looking at what was happening.
That whatever the prophet directed, I would do.
He said, "Affliction!"
Everybody would say, "Go!"
"Affliction!" - I also said the same thing, "Out!"
Venerable Banmah Victor & Wife
Retired Anglican Priest
Emmanuel TV Testimony
At the end of that session, I went into my room.
I started to have a slight pain on my temple.
I struck it a number of times, and the pain ceased.
But following that, immediately, I had some sensation in my nose.
And also following that, my right nostril was blocked.
I didn't know what it was. I thought it was mucus.
So I sucked it into my mouth and spat it out. It was like a twig.
I called my wife and said, "Something has come out from my nose".
We used the torch light. I started to look...
The evidence of what I saw is what is in this bottle.
It's a six-inches long worm.
You can imagine if this is in your body, you cannot live long.
I went to many doctors.
I went to an ENT specialist and she gave me drugs.
I also went to a physician who gave me exactly the same drugs.
They did nothing.
For over two years, I was battling with this problem.
Until that faithful day when I put my hand on the television
and said what the prophet was directing and this worm came out of my body.
Praise the Lord!
Our father, with due respect, ever since this worm came out of you, what are the things you can do now?
I don't stagger and I hear perfectly well.
At that time, I couldn't bite a bone but listen to how I rattle my teeth.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Now, our dear father, what the Lord has done in your life,
what word of advice do you have for all who are listening to you?
Sorry, I have a second testimony.
It follows the same pattern.
The prophet was praying and he said, "Those who eat with dead people in the night..."
I knew that I was eating with dead people in the night in my dreams.
So as he was praying, I was rubbing my stomach downwards.
Then immediately, I felt some movement in my stomach and the urge to go to the toilet.
So I rushed to the toilet and the only thing that came out was a round object as big as a ping-pong,
looking exactly like a walnut.
I didn´t take the picture of that because it was inside the water. Praise the Lord!
Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
And ever since you passed out that stuff, do you still eat with dead people in your dreams?
No dreams anymore.
It happened on the 20th of last month.
Till today, I don't dream of any dead people or eat with them.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
I will refer to the psalmist who said,
"If you hear the voice of God, do not harden your heart".
Today, the voice of God through the prophet is here,
it is louder and clearer and it is heard in all the continents.
So brothers and sisters, why will you not listen to the prophet?
Now, I´m imagining that very shortly, The SCOAN is going to become a pilgrimage destination.
That is, people will come from all over the world - not because they are sick
but to come and taste of what is happening here, to come and taste all the prayers,
to come and taste all the sermons and to come and taste all the teaching.
Brothers and sisters, I call on you. If you are far off, it doesn't matter.
Distance is nothing. It´s not a barrier. I call on you.
God loves you.
Jesus loves you.
The prophet of the Most High God T.B. Joshua also loves you.
He loves you with passion!
Praise the Lord!
My name is Mrs. Christiana Banmah. I'm 66 years old.
I confirm what my husband, my beloved husband, has said to be true.
And now you can see how fit he is, even at the age of 82 - going to 82.
He can chew bones but before this time, he could not do anything. I thank God Almighty!
I give Him the glory for using the great Prophet T.B. Joshua
to do mighty works in this land, in the whole world, in the lives of men and women.
Amen!
I want to seize this opportunity, to use this médium to remind and to advise
the doubting Thomases and the faithless pharisees, in quotes.
God is still saying something.
Don't harden your heart as in the day of provocation.
The purpose of God will be established in this country, in this SCOAN, in the name of Jesús!
God is still saying something so don't harden your heart.
That is the only advice I have for them.
Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
God is still speaking.
He still has plenty of things to tell us.
And you can hear God through the prophet - the prophet of the Most High God.
What he has done for me, mainly through the televisión, it is a miracle.
When I mentioned it to my church - you know our church, you know how they can be.
They don't want to hear about any church where they make progress.
But I said, "No, this is not something I can keep to myself.
I must tell the whole world that there is a man in Nigeria, in Lagos,
in The SCOAN, that can do a lot of things to help humanity.
He has touched my life and he will touch the life of my children as time goes on. Praise the Lord!
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the Miracle-working God!